Jocelyn Pacheco

832-574-8905

Yosbomb@gmail.com

707 Greens Rd, Houston, Tx, 77060

Profile

Experienced bilingual (English-Spanish) effective communicator with inbound and outbound calls agent able to efficiently process a large volume of calls and files in a day. Adept in computer database programs offering exceptional customer service face to face, computer or by phone. Specialize in dealing with angry clients processing large amounts of call data and interpreting customer service data to spreadsheet.

Experience

Inbound call center agent —

Feb 2010 - AgU 2011

Comcast Teleperfomance

Av Lázaro Cárdenas, Zona San Agustín, 64989 Monterrey, N.L.,

Handled inbound customer service complaints and questions from a variety of customers, built customer confidence by actively listening to their concerns and giving appropriate feedback. Input data into the company database and generate reports for management at the end of the week.

- •Facilitating necessary repairs or replacements.
 - •Recording interaction with customers.
 - •Handled inbound calls from prospective clients and tried to turn those
 - ·prospects into paying customers.
 - •Referring customers to appropriate departments to resolve their grievances.
 - •Schedule maintenance calls for customer when they would call in with a

technical issues.

Outbound sales agent

AGU 2011 - OCT 2013

Global tele sourcing

Aaron Saenz #1891-1 Col. Santa María. 64650. Monterrey, NL

Client leads: Direct tv ,Verizon

Addressed and resolved customer issues utilizing effective listening and problem solving skills for Verizon home phone and Direct Tv. Consistently met and exceeded department goals and objectives retaining disgruntled clients who have issues with the companies product.

- •Call potential customers to describe and educate services offered
 - •Placed phone calls to current customers to determine their satisfaction as well as to offer additional services .
 - •Follow up with customers leads or previous customers

INBOUND / OUT BOUND SALES AGENT

Evergreen energy - Global tele sourcing

- •Mastery of customer service call scripts within a specified time frames.
- •Draft emails that can be sent to potential customers education them on the company and what they offer, Explaining to the customer how the company can help them not just sell to them.
 - •Placed calls to inquiring customers.
 - •Processed payment via credit cards.

Insurance agent /In store/ sales representative

DEC 2013 - DEC 2015

Adrianas Insurance

9445 Charles Smith Ave Rancho Cucamonga, CA 91730

Responsible for auto insurance quotes and sales suggested coverage options to better protect customer's assets, Performed constant navigation between multiple open windows on computer while accessing client info, carrier rates/policy information and maintaining a steady and smooth flow of conversation while providing an overall positive and satisfactory experience for the customer.

Ranked among the top Sales Agents

- •Establishing sales techniques and applying my skills to an inbound call center environment.
- •High remarks for customer service and member satisfaction.
- •Trained new sales agents to exceed company goals and metrics.

Production operator, Fresh Dough Facility

JUNE 2016-oCT 2016

Panera bread ,FDF

10351 W Little York Rd ste 100, Houston, TX

Perform food production tasks to create crave-able dough products that are distributed and baked daily. Operating a variety of food manufacturing equipment (mixers, molders, and dishwashers) as well as verifying and correct quantities of loaded bakery in cabinets.

•Preparing cooler with cabinets for morning production.

- •Keeping area safe, clean, and organized, removing empty trays from cabinets.
- •Preparing cooler with cabinets for morning production.

FIREWATCH - KINDER MORGAR

OCT 2016-SEP 2017

PMI (Palacios terminal services),

901 Light Company Rd, Pasadena, TX 77506

Provide assistance to customers, employees and visitors in a courteous and professional manner, watch for irregular or unusual conditions that may create security concerns of safety hazards.

- •Sound alarms of call police or fire department in case of fire or presence of unauthorized persons.
- •Perform security patrols of designated areas on foot or vehicle.
- Permit authorized persons to enter property and monitor entrance and exit.
- •Warn violator of rule infractions, such as loitering, smoking or carrying forbidden articles.

Brand Ambassador - MULTIPLE BRANDS AND ALCOHOL PRODUCTS

April 2018-2018

SALE Liquor store Houston, TX

Face and voice of the company at the store engaging with customers in meaningful ways engaging with store personal and educating them on the features and benefits of the product, Generating new sales opportunities by describing products and building recognition to the brand and the products.

- * Offering and handing out samples
 - •Increasing brand awareness.
 - Helped customers select products that best fit their personal needs.
 - •Communicated information to customers about product quality value and style

Retail agent-In store.

April 2018-

Boost Mobile

708 Greens Rd, Houston, TX 77060

Sign in new plans and new device activations, Assist walk in current and new customers providing profesional customer service by attending needs such as assist with monthly payments, clearing questions and addressing concerns properly.

- •Operating cash register and handling cash.
- •Handling private and personal information.
- Manage store inventory and new orders.

Brand Ambassador- July 2018 -2018

Career Group Companies

Houston, TX

Interviewed individuals through member engagements to collect and record donations using handheld data capture devices, Harmonized with other BAs (brand ambassadors) by meeting for the first time a few minutes prior to working an event together.

- •Promoted Herbalife North America Extravaganza 2018 at NRG Stadium
- •Providing members information of the associations and collecting their donations .
- Assisted in give aways and worked together with co workers to ensure overall visitor satisfaction.
- •Maintained confidentiality and remained oped to ideas.
- •Interacted taking photographs with the visitors as promotional model.

Skills

- •Trained in Bothe sales and customer service departments (Oral and written communication, Active listening)
 - •Outgoing ,Very comfortable with cameras.
 - Years of experience with telesales and telemarketing
 - •45 WPM
 - Microsoft Office suite, Microsoft Outlook, Microsoft Power point, Microsoft Word.
 - •Effective Internet research
 - Outstanding communicator (Opening/Closing procedures)
 - •Experience submitting accurate reports for inventory, payroll hours, and material used.

Education — Monterrey ,NL

• Preparatoria 15 Madero - Universidad Autonoma de Nuevo Leon.

Professional References

Adrianas Insurance Supervisor Mario Villanueva, : 521 (811) 983-7098

Panera Bread FDF: Supervisor Teodosio Lopez:521 (332) 177-100

Career Group Companies: Ashley Didawick: (310) 228-6960 Ext.1151

Global Tele-sourcing: (811)277-6135